The winged knights launch
repeated assaults on Castle Thor,
while Hyura and the other demonkin
fight arduously to fend them off
in a never-ending cycle.
Meanwhile,
Vermilio and company make their way
through a barren desert.
One night, Helck offers his sword to Vermilio
revealing its true nature as
the weapon known as "Hero Slayer."
Listen, I'm going to tell you about my past,
the power of heroes,
and everything else that happened
in the human realm.
Then once you've heard the story,
I'd like you to consider doing me this favor.
Ah, displaying strength like it was totally natural
Feelings of inferiority growing deeper
From the moment of birth
Let them know that it's a done deal
The neighbor to utopia
Despair is saying "hello," ya see
The fact that nobody notices
Is it for better or worse?
No matter how many times I wake up
It's like I'm in a nightmare
If suffering is all there is
Then God could you please
Consider remaking me from scratch?
Ah, for many thousands of years we have
Been holding out hope for the future
The end is bound to come no matter what
And we try to resist it
How many prayers is this now?
Body and soul completely transformed
Just wanting to believe in something even if it's fake
Huh? Am I alive right now?
I don't even know anymore
Help me, I need to be saved
With Younger Brother in Tow
Here. Today's earnings.
What? Just some bread?
Helck (Age 8)
But I worked so hard...
Times are tough for everybody, kid!
Please, you gotta help me out!
Put a sock in it!
Don't bother coming back if you're just gonna whine!
I'm sorry...
No! Please stop it!
That hurts!
Cless (Age 4)
Get a grip!
You better use that thing to block me
unless you wanna die!
Ouch!
Come on!
Take this! And this!
Please stop it!
Big Bro!
Look who's here.
What? You gonna defy our orders now, punk?
There's no chance of that happening.
Yeah, nobody would dare talk back to us!
That's what I thought.
Get on the bad side of nobility like us,
and we'll make sure
you and all the other pieces of human trash
around here get beaten to a bloody pulp.
I won't defy you.
But if you want to hit someone,
then please hit me.
Oh, yeah?
Then don't mind if I do.
Big Bro!
Weakling!
Have a taste of this!
Big Bro...
My younger brother and I
grew up as orphans.
When I was just six years old,
a monster suddenly appeared in our village,
and took the lives of our mother and father.
The village was ravaged.
There was no hope of rebuilding it.
Cless, we're still alive.
And no matter what happens,
we're going to keep on
living for Mom and Dad's sake.
Daddy... Mommy...!
It's all right.
I'm here for you, okay?
I'm going to keep you safe!
We headed for the royal capital.
Because we figured
if any place would have a job
that even kids could do, it would be there.
Take this, loser!
But it turned out
the royal capital was vastly different
from the promised land we imagined.
Economic disparity
was sharply on the rise,
and those who were poor got treated worse
than livestock by the wealthy and affluent.
But in spite of all that, the two of us
decided that's where we would live.
Our home was on the outskirts
of the capital, in the slums.
It was a dismal and unsanitary place,
with hardly a scrap of food
to be found anywhere.
But compared to living with the
danger of being attacked by monsters,
it seemed like the far better option.
Hiyah!
Damn, he's a tough little turd.
My wooden sword actually snapped in two.
Let's go somewhere else.
I don't want their stink
to get on my clothes.
Okay.
See you later, worm boy!
Big Bro!
Getting abused by members of nobility
was a part of everyday life.
But I didn't care as long as Cless was safe.
I would let them tease me
and beat me all they wanted.
Are you okay, Big Bro?
Yeah. Don't worry about me.
I'm sorry, Big Bro!
I never should have looked them in the eyes!
Enough crying. You need to man up, Cless.
I would protect Cless no matter what it took.
That was the one thing I swore to myself.
But you're all bloody and messed up
because of me...
I mean, you could say the same
about yourself.
You're in way worse shape than I am!
I told you not to worry!
You know I'm built tough, right?
Go on. Take a good look.
Super recovery mode.
Gosh, you're so amazing, Big Bro!
Wait a damn minute!
You could do that
when you were just a kid?!
Yep! It came to me naturally.
Hold up, that must mean you had
already awakened your hero powers!
Thinking back on it, you're probably right.
But at the time,
I just thought of myself as being
a little more durable than everybody else.
I wonder when it happened...
I actually don't remember anything
about when I first awakened my powers.
Does that mean he awakened
when he was still just a baby?
In which case, he developed
and matured while totally free
from any of the usual human limitations.
No wonder he's crazy strong.
Sorry about that. Please continue.
Okay, but would you like
more hot cocoa first?
Oh... yes, please.
They continued to torment us
more after that.
Sometimes our food would get
thrown into the river.
And our home would get ransacked
or lit on fire.
There were even times the harassment
from drunk nobles was so bad
I thought they'd kill me.
And on some days,
the meager wages that I had worked
to earn would get taken right from me.
Despite all of that, leaving the
royal capital wasn't an option for us.
Monsters had been spawning
outside of the city in great numbers,
bringing chaos and death in their wake.
So no matter how bad the abuse was,
we had no choice except to stay in the capital.
Nonetheless, our outlook
was always optimistic.
Cless! Bad news!
I only got paid in bread today!
But it's filled with cheese!
Hooray!
That's not all!
I managed to barter for some eggs, too!
Wow, you're so good at bartering!
Such noisy little brats.
I didn't want to sour the mood
by being gloomy.
Cless, the day will come when
there are less monsters around,
and that's when we'll leave.
The two of us will set out on a journey.
A journey?
Yep.
We'll travel the world
until we find a peaceful place
where we can live
without being harassed by anyone.
Okay!
I didn't need a rich and fancy lifestyle.
I just wanted to be with Cless.
As long as the two of us could live happily,
then that was more than enough for me.
But sadly, another tragic event
was waiting for us just around the corner.
Seems like your little brother's immune system
was in poor shape due to malnutrition.
Cless! Hang in there, Cless!
Seems like your little brother's immune system
was in poor shape due to malnutrition.
Cless! Hang in there, Cless!
He's too young to survive an illness like this.
Cless!
He won't last through the night.
No way!
There must be something you can do!
Don't look at me.
I'm not even a doctor, kid.
This is my fault.
I should have done more to keep him fed!
Then he'd be okay!
Don't blame yourself.
That's just how life goes around here.
He's not the only one, you know.
You just gotta chalk it up
to fate and move on.
To hell with fate!
I won't accept it!
I'm not letting Cless die!
Hang tight, Cless.
I'm going to bring a doctor for you right away!
Don't waste your time!
I mean, what can you hope to accomplish
without any money?
I have some that I saved up
for when we were ready to move.
Wait! You shouldn't get your hopes up!
Nobody's gonna go out of their way
to save bottom of the barrel folks like us!
Especially since plenty of them
think we're better off dead in a ditch!
Come back! Just give up!
I knew the old-timer had a point.
But even so,
there was no way I was just going
to stand by and watch Cless die.
I went to house after house.
Excuse me! Please open up!
My little brother is sick!
I don't care. Go away!
Knocking on door after door.
Get lost!
Begging for help over and over.
The less of you bums there are
stinking up the slums, the better!
But...
If you want money, I have some!
And if that's not enough, I swear on my life
I'll bring you more in a day or two!
I'm begging you!
Please just take a look at my brother!
Hey, kid. How'd you get all that money?
Huh?
There's no way some brat from the slums
would have this kind of money.
Where'd you steal it from?!
B-but I didn't!
I've been earning it
little by little each day...
Hey! Call the guards!
We've got a thief here!
No...
No!
I kept on trying.
I didn't want to give up.
Big Bro...
Sorry about this, Cless.
Just hold on a little longer.
I'm sorry... Big Bro...
I'm always causing trouble for you...
Don't be silly.
You've never caused me trouble before.
Not even once.
Keep your spirits up.
I'm definitely going to find you
a doctor, okay?
Okay...
What do you say we leave here
once the weather warms up?
It's hard to get our hands on
any food these days.
And since we get harassed all the time,
things might actually be better
if we tried living with the monsters!
Remember what I told you before?
About how we'd travel
and find a peaceful place?
That's where we'll live.
I know the monsters and bandits
might be scary, but it'll be okay!
I'm gonna put on muscle
until I'm strong enough to beat them,
and then send them all packing!
Big Bro...
I'm always going to be there
to protect you, okay?
Cless?
Stay with me!
You can't die in a place like this!
I started running frantically.
And sought help from anyone who I came across.
Somebody help! Please, I need help!
My little brother is sick!
I have some money!
Please take me to a doctor!
I'm begging you!
My brother needs help!
Somebody please save Cless!
Goddamn slum vermin!
Don't spread your diseases around here!
Go back where you came from!
Please help...
Please... help Cless...
Dammit! Dammit...
Hey, little guy. What's the matter?
What's the matter?
A noble...
You were shouting just a minute ago.
What's going on?
My little brother is close to dying
because of an illness.
I need help! Please!
Save my brother...
She just wanted to torment me...
Dammit... Dammit!
Hey, Father! Listen! It's an emergency!
There's this grubby and ragged kid
over there who's about to die!
Jeez, I really need to teach you
to have a little more tact in public...
Hurry up! He's gonna die!
What's wrong? Are you okay?
This boy is very emaciated.
Let's get him to a doctor right away.
Prepare the coach!
But, sir, that will make you late to the party...
Just tell them that
I won't be attending tonight.
As you wish.
Cless just barely survived the night.
It was so close that any later
and he would have died.
The man who saved us was a noble.
A member of the same hierarchy
that had made our lives a living hell.
Thank you, sir! Thank you so much!
But at that point,
none of it really mattered to me.
Thank you, sir! Thank you so much!
Gratitude was the only thing I felt.
I can't thank you enough!
Thank you so much! Thank you so much!
From the day that we met those nobles,
our futures started to change drastically.
Thank you so much...
From the day that we met those nobles,
our futures started to change drastically.
15 Years Later
We can't hold the line any longer!
Order a retreat!
Don't be stupid!
There'll be nowhere left for us to go
if they break through here!
I know!
But it's impossible to defeat these
monsters with the troops we have left!
Retreating is not an option!
Now act like a soldier
and keep fighting until the last man!
N-no way! I don't wanna die!
Have no fear!
He took it down with one hit...
We're saved! It's Cless!
Captain Cless of the
Third Infantry Regiment is here!
Cless (Age 18)
We will defend this position!
Cover us from the rear.
Yessir!
U-uh...
Leave no monster standing!
Third Infantry Regiment!
Follow my lead!
We'll join the charge, too!
Captain Cless!
We love you!
Helck (Age 22)
The nobleman who saved Cless was
a member of the prestigious Raphaed family,
who've supported the royal family
since the kingdom's founding.
On that day I sought help,
the one and only person who
heard me out was their eldest daughter,
Daughter of Nobility
Shalamy
Shalamy.
Hey!
Do you guys wanna play with me?
For whatever reason, she came to visit us
even after Cless got better
Yeah, that sounds fun.
For whatever reason, she came to visit us
even after Cless got better
What do you want to play?
and became our playmate.
She was an odd ball
who never discriminated against the people
of the slum and just treated us normally.
Let's race!
After we started spending more time with her,
the number of nobles who harassed us
became few and far between.
They must have figured
we were Shalamy's friends,
or actually, servants who
were working in her service.
No matter the case,
it was truly comforting to me.
But it left Cless with
a gloomy look on his face.
Other people who we knew from the slums
were still facing awful hardships.
That fact unsettled Cless
and made him unable to take
any pleasure from our new situation.
Remember what the old-timer said?
As long as monsters plague the kingdom,
the people of the capital
will always be stressed out.
Right.
And without any room to breathe,
everyone will be focused on living their own lives,
so even if someone tried to start a movement
against ending discrimination,
nobody would join in.
Right.
Once the threat of the monsters goes away,
and tensions ease up in the kingdom,
then the capital will become
a much better place!
Right.
Big Bro, I wanna become
a soldier someday!
Huh?!
I'm going to train to be an upstanding warrior
just like Shalamy's dad!
And free everyone from
the terror of the monsters!
Okay then!
At the age of five, Cless began
following a path of his own choosing.
And from that point onward,
he would train his body every day without fail.
He joined the army at 16,
and by the time he turned 18 he had
already been promoted to the rank of Captain.
Wow. Great view from up here.
Oh hey! Nice to see you, Mr. Raphaed!
Greetings, Helck.
I happened to catch sight of you
while passing by.
Have you been well?
Yes!
It looks like Cless has really made
a name for himself this time.
Whenever he goes out on the battlefield,
I get the feeling the kingdom
grows a little bit brighter.
Actually, it's more than just a feeling.
The people of the kingdom have been
totally won over by his charisma.
That tiny boy from all those years ago
grew into a warrior capable
of easily defeating monsters that
any regular soldier would struggle against.
Hell, I don't think even I could compete
with him at this point.
That's impossible.
You're giving him too much credit!
You don't have to humor me.
Cless still has the potential to grow stronger.
And I have no doubt that he will.
I would even go as far as to say that Cless
may become the savior of this kingdom.
A savior, you really think so?
That idea is a lot to chew on!
Helck! Where did Helck get off to?!
He better stop slacking off!
Uh-oh.
I need to get back to work.
Sorry to take up your time.
By the way, Helck.
Yes?
There's something special about you, too.
I can feel an indescribable power within you.
Although, it may just be
my imagination at work.
But I'm willing to bet that you're
just as strong as Cless is.
Don't be ridiculous!
I'm just a beefy guy because of
all the hard labor that I've been doing.
And besides, my swordsmanship
pales in comparison to Cless.
I'm an absolute amateur
when it comes to fighting.
Casualties from monster attacks
are on the rise of late.
There wouldn't be as much to worry about if we had
another powerful man like Cless on our side.
Just a thought I had.
I'm sorry.
But it turns out that I'm just better suited
to doing construction work
and repairs like I am now.
Fair enough.
That's an important job in its own right.
Keep at it!
Thinking about it now,
that man was probably
picking up on my hero powers,
even though I hadn't noticed them myself yet.
Is that Cless and Shalamy?
Oh, my.
Oh, my, my!
I might be crazy, but I think
the flowers of love are in bloom.
Those two actually might
be more than just friends.
But wait, since when?
She's from a prestigious family of nobles.
So it's gonna be a tough road for them.
But as his big brother,
I'm gonna lend Cless my full support!
Hey, Cless?
Your brother's standing here all alone
with a huge grin on his face.
My brother's smile is perpetual.
You two are always in
a real chipper mood, huh?
Hey, there! Shalamy and Cless!
Thanks for waiting.
I stumbled into Shalamy on my way here.
I'm gonna join in on your fun!
Circumstances had forced
Cless and I to live apart
I'm gonna join in on your fun!
Circumstances had forced
Cless and I to live apart
The more the merrier!
ever since he became a member of the army.
Let's hit up the usual place, Helck.
Sure!
Although we didn't see each other often,
we would occasionally find some time
to meet up and have dinner together.
Cheers!
The days that the
three of us spent together
were some of the most enjoyable
that I can remember.
Helck, I'm going to be leaving the capital for
another expedition the day after tomorrow.
The monsters that we've been assigned
to take care of are particularly troublesome,
so I might not be able
to come home for some time.
Oh, really?
Well, I'm not worried.
I know you're skilled enough
to bring down any monster.
Just be careful not to go overboard.
If anything happened, I wouldn't be
the only person here to mourn your loss.
Huh?
Oh, of course.
When I get back, I'd really love to have
some of your home cooking.
Roger that!
Then you can count on one of my
special stamina-booster meals
to be waiting on the table for you!
Make sure you come back alive!
Right!
However...
we never got the chance to have
that welcome back party,
because I couldn't stick around.
Hey, what was that dream
We used to fantasize about?
A treasured memory even if it's small
And covered in mud
I was so clumsy that
I couldn't even tell left from right
When those clear eyes took my hand and saved me
It's okay, it's okay, you kept saying
As you hugged me tightly over and over
This time I will be the one to grab ahold
Of your warm hand
I shouted your name and the world laughed
Those words that hold us together
Are the most precious of all
If this is going to be our fate, then let's change it
On the other side of the darkness
We shall seize the light together
Next Episode
The Mercenaries
Next time: "The Mercenaries"