The winged knights launch
repeated assaults on Castle Thor,
while Hyura and the other demonkin
fight arduously to fend them off
in a never-ending cycle.
Meanwhile,
Vermilio and company make their way
through a barren desert.
One night, Helck offers his sword to Vermilio
revealing its true nature as
the weapon known as "Hero Slayer."
Listen, I'm going to tell you about my past,
the power of heroes,
and everything else that happened
in the human realm.
Then once you've heard the story,
I'd like you to consider doing me this favor.
Ah, displaying strength like it was totally natural
Feelings of inferiority growing deeper
From the moment of birth
Let them know that it's a done deal
The neighbor to utopia
Despair is saying "hello," ya see
The fact that nobody notices
Is it for better or worse?
No matter how many times I wake up
It's like I'm in a nightmare
If suffering is all there is
Then God could you please
Consider remaking me from scratch?
Ah, for many thousands of years we have
Been holding out hope for the future
The end is bound to come no matter what
Helck (Age 22)
Daughter of Nobility
Shalamy
Next Episode
The Mercenaries